A Guide to the Richmond (Va.), Bureau of Permits and Inspections, Building permit architectural blueprints and specifications, 1907-1976
Library of Virginia
- Blueprint drawings, 1907-1950, 3167 sets of blueprints
  - Bank buildings, 1909-1948
    - Bank - Permit Number: 2251, Building for First National Bank Building Corporation, Address: SW corner 9th and Main Sts., 1911 (Folder 167)
      Drawn by: Clinton & Russell, 32 Nassau Street, New York City, Alfred C. Bossom, 366 Fifth Avenue, New York City; Contractor: G. A. Fuller; Commissioned by: First National Bank Corporation; Notes: Blueprints on drafting cloth.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 2596, Store Building at the N. W. Corner of Broad & 6th Sts., for the Broad Street Bank, Address: N. side Broad St. between 5th and 6th Sts., 1911 (Folder 199)
      Drawn by: Noland & Baskervill, Architects, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Slaughter and Perrin; Commissioned by: Broad Street Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 2833, Mechanics and Merchants Bank, Address: Corner of Hull and 12th St., 1912 (Folder 356)
      Drawn by: Albert F. Huntt, Architect, 1107 East Main St., Richmond; Contractor: J. T. Nuckols; Commissioned by: Mechanics and Merchants Bank; Notes: Brick, stone and concrete bank building designed in an exuberant rendition of the Renaissance Revival style. Good details of interior cornice and pilasters. CD # 93.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 2024, Alterations for a New Banking Room for the National State and City Bank, Address: 1111 E. Main St., 1912 (Folder 302)
      Drawn by: Clinton & Russell, Architects, 32 Nassau Street, New York City; Contractor: Jno. T. Wilson Co., Inc. Contractors; Commissioned by: National State and City Bank; Notes: Repairs to a bank building in the 1100 block of East Main where Clinton and Russell were very active at the time. A New York firm, C and R designed the most important early 20th century high-rise office buildings in Richmond.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 6010A, Alterations and Additions to Building for the Central National Bank, Address: NW corner of Broad and 3rd Sts. (222-224 East Broad), 1916 (Folder 664)
      Drawn by: Charles M. Robinson; Contractor: W. L. Ragland; Commissioned by: Central National Bank; Notes: Alterations and additions to the first level of a bank building. Excellent interior details for vault, teller spaces, and other bank related areas. The bank was demolished and replaced by The Virginia Federal Savings & Loan Bank when the Central National Bank (a.k.a. Central Fidelity) constructed a new building in 1929 at 219 E. Broad.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 6838A, Alterations and Additions to Merchants National Bank, Address: 1101 E. Main St., 1918 (Folder 1344)
      Drawn by: J. T. Nuckols; Contractor: J. T. Nuckols; Commissioned by: Merchants National Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 6101, Building for West End Bank, Address: 1300 W. Main St., 1918 (Folder 1301)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., General Contractors, 2510 West Main St.; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: West End Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 007023, Virginia Trust Company, Address: S/S E. Main St. between 8th and 9th, 1919 (Folder 769)
      Drawn by: Carneal and Johnston with Alfred C. Bossom; Contractor: Jo-; Commissioned by: Virginia Trust Company; Notes: Very fragile plans for a Classical Revival bank building.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 8199A, Bank of Commerce and Trusts, Address: NE corner of 12th and Hull St., Southside Richmond, 1919 (Folder 498)
      Drawn by: Max E. Ruehrmund; Contractor: John T. Wilson Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Bank of Commerce and Trusts; Notes: 2-level brick and stone bank building designed in Max Ruehrmund's interpretation of the American Renaissance Revival. A granite base supports the front elev. composed of double Corinthian pilasters which flank the central entry over which rises an arched window with center clock detail.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 08051A, Alterations and Additions to Planters National Bank, Address: 1200 E. Main St., 1919 (Folder 766)
      Drawn by: Carneal and Johnston with Alfred C. Bossom; Contractor: John T. Wilson; Commissioned by: Planters National Bank; Notes: Excellent details of the alterations to the "main banking room" executed in stone and designed with classical motifs such as Corinthian columns and pilasters, arched windows, and paneled walls.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 6387, American Trust Company, Address: 1005 E. Main St., 1919 (Folder 1334)
      Drawn by: Mowbray & Uffinger, 56 Liberty St., New York, Carneal & Johnston, Architects, Richmond, Va., Associate Architects; Contractor: A. F. Perrin; Commissioned by: American Trust Co.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 8750A, Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, Address: NW corner of Ninth and Franklin Sts., 1920 (Folder 717)
      Drawn by: Sill, Buckler & Fenhagen, Architects, Baltimore; Contractor: J. T. Wilson and Co.; Commissioned by: Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond; Notes: Brick, stone and steel bank building. This is the Old Federal Reserve Bank which was received an annex and additions by Carneal & Johnston three years later in 1922.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 9334A, Plans for Remodeling Church Hill Bank, Broad & 25th Sts., Address: 2500 E. Broad St., 1920 (Folder 477)
      Drawn by: Bascom J. Rowlett, Architect, Richmond, VA.; Contractor: James Fox and Sons; Commissioned by: Church Hill Bank; Notes: Specifications are on the stationary of Albert F. Huntt. These specifications call (among other changes) for the demolition and replacement of the entire front wall of this building.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 7354, Bank Building for the Richmond Beneficial Insurance Company, Address: 702 North 2nd St. St., 1920 (Folder 236)
      Drawn by: Charles T. Russell, Architect; Contractor: D. J. Farrar, Cont.; Commissioned by: Richmond Beneficial Insurance Company; Notes: Neoclassical 2-story savings bank building built of granite and brick. Narrow front elevation shows stone pilasters flanking a paneled door and flat roof.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 10660A, Alterations and Additions to Broadway National Bank, Address: 1426 E. Main St., 1921 (Folder 741)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: W. L. Ragland; Commissioned by: Broadway National Bank Building; Notes: Alterations and additions to a Neoclassical Revival bank building.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 8721, Branch Bank for American National Bank, Address: SW corner Floyd Ave. and Robinson St., 1921 (Folder 710)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Lambert; Contractor: Hunt and Amrhein; Commissioned by: American National Bank; Notes: Stone and stucco bank building with classical flat roof and cornice. The central entrance show a Palladian door embellished with Baroque elements and crowned with a segmented pediment topped by an eagle. The building is used currently (2000) as a gallery and frame company.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 7936, Office Building for the Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, Address: 8th and Franklin Sts., 1921 (Folder 464)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: John T. Wilson Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Federal Reserve Bank; Notes: These plans are for the original version of this building which had three bays on the Eighth and Ninth streets elevations. The Federal Reserve was later expanded on the north side of the building.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 10806A, Alterations, The Union Bank of Richmond, Address: 1104 E. Main St., 1922 (Folder 756)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: J. W. Atkinson; Commissioned by: Union Bank; Notes: Excellent details of classical elements added to the entrance of a stone bank.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 10312, Branch Office Planters National Bank, Address: 108 E. Broad St., 1922 (Folder 802)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Davis Bros., Inc.; Commissioned by: Planters National Bank; Notes: This Neo-Classical Revival bank building is one in a row of buildings, 102-110 East Broad Street, that was refaced in 1976.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 10478, The Savings Bank of Richmond, Address: SW corner of 12th and Main Sts., 1922 (Folder 808)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Lambert; Contractor: W. L. Ragland and Son; Commissioned by: Savings Bank of Richmond; Notes: Two story brick bank building with a narrow front and long side plan. The facade is a stone Neo-Classical Revival configuration with central double doors flanked by Corinthian pilasters.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 09719, Bank and Office Building for Richmond Trust Co., Address: 7th and Main St., 1922 (Folder 759)
      Drawn by: Starrett & Van Vleck, Architects, NYC; Contractor: John T. Wilson; Commissioned by: Richmond Trust Co.; Notes: Ten story Classical Revival bank building.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 10126, Church Hill Office, American National Bank, Address: 25th and Marshall Sts., 1922 (Folder 800)
      Drawn by: Charles M. Robinson; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American National Bank; Notes: Brick bank building designed in a Neoclassical Revival style with relief panels with eagles in the frieze.
    - Bank - Permit Number: N/A, Grace Street Bank and Trust Building, Address: 301 - 303 E. Grace St., 1923 (Folder 1430)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Grace Street Bank and Trust Co.; Notes: Once owned by the Reynolds Metals Corp., then Media General, this building was demolished 1999.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 11397, Changes to the North Side Branch of State & City Bank & Trust, Address: 2930 North Ave., 1923 (Folder 856)
      Drawn by: Lee & Lee; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: State & City Bank & Trust; Notes: Alterations and the additions of a store and second story apartment to an existing Classical Revival Bank building.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 12061, Bank and Office Building for the State and City Bank and Trust Company, Address: Ninth and Main Sts., 1924 (Folder 1061)
      Drawn by: Clinton & Russell; Contractor: John T. Wilson; Commissioned by: State and City Bank and Trust; Notes: Early 1920s skyscraper built of limestone. Ornament is sparingly used. The giant Ionic colonnade with a cast iron window screen to the rear is the focal point of the facade.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 11390, Building for the Broad Street Bank, Address: 528-30 Broad St., 1924 (Folder 546)
      Drawn by: Clinton & Russell, 100 Maiden Lane, New York, N.Y.; Contractor: Jas. Fox and Sons; Commissioned by: Broad Street Bank; Notes: One story stone building designed in the Renaissance Revival mode and to add a later second story.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 14489, Highland Park Office Merchants National Bank, Address: 1307 Brookland Park Blvd., 1925 (Folder 1147)
      Drawn by: William C. West, Architect, 1103 East Main Street, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: F. H. Boatwright; Commissioned by: Merchants National Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 14470A, Alterations to the Bargamin Building, Address: 14 - 16 South 9th St., 1926 (Folder 1576)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: O. C. Peters; Commissioned by: First National Bank Bldg.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 14830A, Alterations to 408 E. Broad St., for Morris Plan Bank, Address: 408 E. Broad St., 1926 (Folder 1274)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: T. L. Moore; Commissioned by: Henry Tobin Est.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 15915A, Alterations - Union Bank & Federal Trust Co., Address: 1104 E. Main St., 1927 (Folder 1629)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Union Bank & Federal Trust Co.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 17755, Plans of North Side Office, American National Bank, Address: 201 W. Brookland Park Blvd., 1927 (Folder 1679)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, 701 Grace-American Building, Richmond; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American National Bank; Notes: CD # 82.
    - Bank - Permit Number: 16825A, Addition to Bank & Office Building for Richmond Trust Co., Address: 627 - 633 E. Main St., 1928 (Folder 1729)
      Drawn by: Starret & Van Vleck, Architects, 393 Seventh Avenue, New York; Contractor: Wise Granite Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Richmond Trust Building Corp.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 20173, Office Building for Building & Loan Association of Richmond - 302 E. Grace St., Address: 302 E. Grace St., 1929 (Folder 1851)
      Drawn by: L. P. Hartsook, Edw. F. Sinnott, Associated Architects, American National Bank Bldg., Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: B. & L. Realty Corp.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: N/A, Central National Bank Building, Address: 219 E. Broad St., 1929 (Folder 1849)
      Drawn by: John Eberson, New York City, Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Richmond, Virginia, Associate Architects; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Central National Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 18040A, Alterations to Banking Room of American Bank and Trust Company, S. E. Corner 10th and Main Sts., Address: 1001 E. Main St., 1930 (Folder 1829)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American Bank and Trust Co.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 20846, Southside Branch for American Bank and Trust Company, Address: 1518, 1520, 1522 Hull St., 1930 (Folder 1825)
      Drawn by: Uffinger, Foster and Bookwalter, Inc., Architects, 221 W. 57th St., New York City; Hartsook and Sinnott Associate Architects, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American Office Building Corp.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 21998, The Morris Plan Bank of Virginia, Address: 800 - 812 E. Main St., 1931 (Folder 1873)
      Drawn by: Hoggson Brothers, New York, Chicago; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Morris Plan Holding Co.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 23119A, Alterations to Building #222 - 224 E. Broad St., for Central National Bank, Address: 224 E. Broad St., 1936 (Folder 2077)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Central National Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 24322, Dry Cleaning Plant, 2703 and 2705 West Broad St., Address: 2705 W. Broad St., 1937 (Folder 1999)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: State Planters Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 26743A, Alterations and Additions at 105 E. Grace St., Address: 105 E. Grace St., 1940 (Folder 2167)
      Drawn by: City Building Co.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Guaranty Trust Co.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 25518, Alterations and Additions to First & Merchants National Bank, Address: 10, 12, 14, 16 South 9th St., 1940 (Folder 2151)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: First & Merchants National Bank of Richmond; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 25710, Franklin Federal Savings and Loan Association of Richmond, Address: 616 E. Franklin St., 1940 (Folder 2114)
      Drawn by: Edward F. Sinnott - Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Franklin - Davis Corp.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 27894A, Alterations to the Bank of Commerce & Trust, 16th and Hull Streets, Address: 1518 Hull St., 1941 (Folder 2248)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects and Engineers; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Bank of Commerce & Trust Co.; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 27417A, Alterations and Additions to the Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, Address: 100-106 N. Ninth St., 1941 (Folder 2204)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston, & Wright, Architects & Engineers; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Unknown; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 34699A, Alterations to Richmond Federal Savings and Loan Association, Address: 8th and Main St., 1947 (Folder 2748)
      Drawn by: Louis W. Ballou and Charles C. Justice, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Federal Savings and Loan; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 28743, First and Merchants National Bank, Robinson and Broad Street, Address: 2601 W. Broad St., 1947 (Folder 2689)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: First & Merchants; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 34955A, Addition to Building, First and Merchants Branch Bank, Highland Park, Address: 1307 E. Brookland Blvd., 1948 (Folder 3133)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; American Furniture & Fixture Co., Inc., Designers & Consultants, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: First & Merchants Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 35087A, First Federal Savings and Loan Co., Duct Work Layout, Address: 3rd and Broad Sts., 1948 (Folder 3023)
      Drawn by: Catlett-Johnson Corporation, 1309 West Main Street, Richmond 20, VA; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: First Federal Savings; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 29817, Building for the Bank of Virginia, Grace and Fourth Sts., Address: 401-03 E. Grace St., 1948 (Folder 3110)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Son, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Bank of Virginia; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 29314, Branch Office, State Planters Bank and Trust Co. to be located at Broad St. and Summit Ave., Address: 3022 W. Broad St., 1948 (Folder 2976)
      Drawn by: Huff, Mcfarlane, and Associates, Architects and Engineers, 103A E. Clay St., Richmond, Va; C. W. Huff, Jr., Architect.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: State Planters Bank; Notes:
    - Bank - Permit Number: 34928A, The Bank of Virginia, Address: 2900-02 W. Broad St., 1948 (Folder 3131)
      Drawn by: Slaughter, Saville & Blackburn, Inc., Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Bank of Virginia; Notes:
  - Cemeteries, 1924-1931
    Blueprints of work in cemeteries in Richmond (Va.). Generally contatins permit number; street address; date; name of architiect who drew the blueprints; name of contractor; number of commissioner of the work; and additional notes.
    - Cemetery - Permit Number: 12482A, Building for L.A. Jenkins, Inc., Address: 2221 W. Broad St., 1924 (Folder 1035)
      Drawn by: Charles M. Robinson; Contractor: A. M. Walkup; Commissioned by: L. H. Jenkins; Notes: Two-story, brick commercial building.
    - Cemetery - Permit Number: 21602, Elevations and Plans of Walls- Holy Cross Cemetery, Address: 1700 Mathews St., 1931 (Folder 1822)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Holy Cross Cemetery; Notes:
  - Charitable Organizations, 1907-1947
    Blueprints of work for charitable organizations in Richmond (Va.). Generally contatins permit number; street address; date; name of architiect who drew the blueprints; name of contractor; number of commissioner of the work; and additional notes.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 69, Building for the Railroad Branch Y. M. C. A. at Main Street and Market Slip, Address: 17th and Main Sts., 1907 (Folder 185)
      Drawn by: Wilson, Harris, and Richards, Architects, Drexel Building, Philadelphia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: C. Lorraine, Chairman [Young Men's Christian Association]; Notes: This is the building on Main Street between Main Street Station and the Farmer's Market. Unusual in that 11 sections, elevations, and plans are shown on two sheets. Design shows game rooms on first floor, class rooms on second floor, and dormitories on third floor.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 687, Young Men's Christian Association, Address: N. side Grace St. between 6th. And 7th. Sts., 1908 (Folder 160)
      Drawn by: Wm. C. West, Richmond, Va., Seymour Davis & Paul Davis 3rd., 1600 South Chestnut St. Phila., Pa., Architects; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Young Men's Christian Association; Notes:
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 2921, Y.W.C.A. Boarding Home, Address: Cary St. between Adams & Jefferson, 1912 (Folder 159)
      Drawn by: Noland & Baskervill, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: E. C. Woodward, Contractor; Commissioned by: Young Men's Christian Association; Notes: Four-story brick dormitory. Front elevation shows 1st and 2nd floors delineated with separate porches. 1st floor porch supported with Doric columns, 2nd floor with Ionic, showing consideration of decor/rightness. The building is otherwise plain with a flat roof and stone lintels over the windows. Interior features dining room, bedrooms and toilet area on first floor. Other floors contain dormitory sleeping rooms and cubicles.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 8905, Boys Club, Address: 408 N. 12th St., Richmond, 1921 (Folder 515)
      Drawn by: R. M. Anderson & Co., Engineers and Contractors, Suite 202 Lyric Bldg., Richmond; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: Boys Club; Notes: 2-story brick and stone building with flat roof designed with classical elements.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 8145, Cottage at Virginia Conference Orphanage, Address: 3200 W. Broad St., 1921 (Folder 585)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Moore and Harry; Commissioned by: Virginia Conference (Methodist Church?); Notes: Two story Colonial Revival dormitory/residence constructed of brick with stone quoin corners.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 8087, Reception Building, Children's Home Society of Virginia, Address: 616 Fourquean Lane, Highland Park,, 1921 (Folder 587)
      Drawn by: A. Carl Messerschmidt; Contractor: R. M. Anderson and Co.; Commissioned by: Children's Home Society of Virginia; Notes: Two story brick Colonial Revival orphanage building with reception area, living room, dining room, and separate spaces for nurses, boys, girls, infants, matrons and recreation.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 9931, Memorial Home for Girls, Address: 1509 Front St., 1922 (Folder 696)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: Memorial Home for Girls; Notes: Brick dormitory designed in the Colonial Revival style.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 13593, Richmond Male Orphanage, Address: 1850 Amelia St,., 1924 (Folder 914)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: J. T. Wilson; Commissioned by: Richmond Male Orphanage Society; Notes: One-level over basement brick building with varying roof lines and floor-ceiling Palladian windows repeated in intervals around the full circumference of the building.
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 14031A, Alterations and Additions - Arents Free Library, Address: 224 South Cherry, 1925 (Folder 1400)
      Drawn by: Charles M. Robinson, Architects, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: James Fox; Commissioned by: Grace E. Arents; Notes:
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 18291A, New Stairway for Little Sisters of the Poor, Address: Between Main and Floyd, Plum and Harvie Sts., 1930 (Folder 1814)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Little Sisters of the Poor; Notes:
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 21627, Home for Needy Confederate Women, Address: 301 N. Sheppard St., 1931 (Folder 1818)
      Drawn by: Lee, Smith & Van Dervoort, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: A. J. Saville; Commissioned by: Home for Needy Confederate Women; Notes:
    - Charitable - Permit Number: 22547, Community Recreation Center, Address: 1009 St. Paul St., 1932 (Folder 1888)